

NATALIA SZLAG UX/UI Designer



nataliaszlag.github.io



606-354-801



nataliaszlag@gmail.com

SKILLS

WIREFRAMING
PROTOTYPING
MOCKUPS
GRAPHIC DESIGN
DESIGN RESEARCH
RWD
HTML & CSS
SCRUM
TEAM PLAYER
ENGLISH C1

TOOLS

CORELDRAW

FIGMA

ADOBE XD

GITHUB

PROFILE

I am designer with 3 years of professional experience in User Interface Design. I love challenging myself with unique and pixel-perfect projects. I am looking forward to develop myself in UX/UI world. I am confident that my skills and attitude will boost your team.

EXPERIENCE

Owner / Product Designer 2018 - present | KRAFT DESIGN

Creating products for clients following UCD philosphy. Cooperating with front-end developers and customers during development stages. Presenting complex mockups to customers. Designing over 500 unique designs using CorelDraw and Figma.

Reporting Specialist 2015 - 2018 | UBS, Capgemini, Capita

Producing and analyzing financial reports in cooperation with international departments. Taking care of ad-hoc analysis. Being an active member of regular team meetings. Cooperating with various customers from all over the world.

EDUCATION

Modern Computer Graphics 2017 - 2018 | AGH University in Cracow

Economic Analytics 2011 - 2016 | Cracow University of Economics

HOBBIES







My Cavalier